Here are three procedures to have a dust rag ready at all times.
First of all.
Take a clean jar.
Spray it with your favorite dusting oil.
Put a clean lint free rag inside of the jar.
Close it.
Leave it overnight.
The rag will absorb the oils and you will have a dusting rag ready at all times.
Plus, it's safe because it's keeping the oils enclosed inside the jar.
You can do the same thing with a plastic bag.
Just spray the inside of the bag.
Put your rag inside.
Close it and it's ready at all times with the oil ready to pickup the dust.
Believe it or not, dryer sheets, fragranced at that.
You have them.
You can dust and you can smell the fragrant and they pick up the dust.